Guide to the Sydney Nathans Collection, 1975-2018 UA.29.02.0130
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- A Mind To Stay Interviews and Transcripts, 1965-2018
  - Jospeh Phillips, 1983 July 1; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0076)
  - Joseph Prather, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Joseph Prather; Lim Cabbil, 1983 June 29; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0049)
  - Joseph Prather, 1983 June 29; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0118)
  - Louis Rainey: Funeral Service, undated (Box 4)
  - Louis Rainey: Interviews (1 of 3), 1978-1986 (Box 4)
  - Louis Rainey: Interviews (2 of 3), 1978-1986 (Box 4)
  - Louis Rainey: Interviews (3 of 3), 1978-1986 (Box 4)
  - Louis Rainey Notes and Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Elmo Rainey: Louis Rainey Interviews, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - Elmo Rainey, undated (Box 4)
  - L. Rainey, 1978 August 18; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0005)
  - L. Rainey, 1978 August 18; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0006)
  - Louis Rainey; Alice Hargress, 1978 August 19; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0007)
  - Louis Rainey; Martin Bond, 1981 May 15, 1981 May 18; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0075)
  - E. Rainey and Lilliemae Cannon Store; Howard Smith and Banks Home, 1981 November 2; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0107)
  - L. Rainey (Tape 1), 1981 November 21; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0114)
  - L. Rainey (Tape 2), 1981 November 21; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0115)
  - L. Rainey and E. Banks, 1981 November 21-22; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0113)
  - Elmira Willis; Louis Rainey, 1981 November 23; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0045)
  - L. Rainey (Tape 3), 1981 November 23; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0116)
  - Bessie Rainey Gay (Tape 1 of 2)), 1981 November 7; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0151)
  - Bessie Rainey Gay (Tape 2 of 2), 1981 November 7; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0152)
  - Louie Rainey, Miss Rosie Rainey, 1983 July; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0091)
  - Louis Rainey Tape 2, 1983 June 20; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0066)
  - Louis Rainey, 1983 June 22; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0078)
  - Louis Rainey and Joel Wallace, 1983 June 22; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0080)
  - Louis Rainey, 1983 June 22; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0093)
  - Louis Rainey, 1983 June 22; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0094)
  - Louis Rainey; Richard Jones; Reunion, 1986 June 3-4; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0070)
  - Gates Rainier, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - Gates Rainier Jr., 1981 May 20; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0041)
  - Katie and Nathaniel Richardson (1 of 3), 1981 April 21; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0014)
  - Katie and Nathaniel Richardson (2 of 3), 1981 April 21; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0015)
  - Katie and Nathaniel Richardson (3 of 3), 1981 April 21; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0016)
  - Katie and Nathaniel Richardson, 1981 November 10; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0129)
  - Hester Hall; Nat and Kate Richardson, 1981 November 10; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0155)
  - Nat and Katie Mae Richardson, 1988 July 7; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0042)
  - Nat and Katie Mae Richardson, 1988 July 7; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0043)
  - Daughter: Nat and Katie Mae Richardson, 1988 July 7; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0046)
  - Memphis and Richardson, undated; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0098)
  - Will Dunn; Nat and Katie Richardson, audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0020)
  - Janie Cameron Riley, 1982; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0052)
  - Louvenia Robertson, 2011 (Box 4)
  - Henry and Louvenia Robertson, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Tom Ruffin Interview, undated (Box 4)
  - Tom Ruffin: Bob Davis, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Tom Ruffin Material, undated (Box 4)
  - Tom Ruffin: Alabama Source Material, 1957-1990 (Box 4)
  - Eugene Sawyer, undated (Box 4)
  - Howard Smith (2 of 2); A. Banks; M. Williams, 1981 May 21; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0051)
  - Sledge Family: Nate, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Sledge Family: Home, undated (Box 4)
  - Sledge Family: Ernest and Mary-Francis, 1983 June 22 (Box 4)
  - Sledge Family: Genealogy, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Ernest and Mary Frances Sledge; Louis Rainey, 1983 June 22; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0077)
  - Alice's Sister, Laura Sledge; Alice's Great Aunt Cabbil, undated; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0025)
  - Howard Smith (1 of 2), 1981 May 21; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0050)
  - Mrs. Rose E. Taylor, 1981 November 15; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0132)
  - C. Thigpen, Spot Williams, B. Murphy, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Charles Tisdale, 1978 November 18; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0018)
  - Walter Francis: Gaillard, "Cradle of Freedom", undated (Box 4)
  - Walter Francis: Reflection, undated (Box 4)
  - Betty Washington: Bud Interviews, 1983 June (Box 4)
  - Betty Washington: Leavie Sledge Address, undated (Box 4)
  - Betty Washington: Helen Washington Sledge, 1982 February 12 (Box 4)
  - Betty Washington and Minnie Williams, undated (Box 4)
  - Porch Interview: Williams/Washington Banks, 1978 August 17; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0003)
  - Porch Interview: Washington, Williams, Banks, Davis, Hargress, 1978 August 18; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0004)
  - B. Washington et. al., 1978 August 19; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0009)
  - Addie Witted, 1989 November 15; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0123)
  - Mrs. Henry Wolfe, 1981 November 3; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0019)
  - Mrs. Henry Wolfe, 1981 November 3; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0134)
  - Civil Rights Timeline, 2011 (Box 4)
  - Greensboro Watchmen, 1964-1965, 2012 (Box 5)
  - Greensboro Watchmen: Notes and Stories, 1965 August-1965 December (Box 5)
  - Theresa Burroughs, 2011 (Box 5)
  - Civil Rights Movement: William Christian Interview, 1979 August 10 (Box 5)
  - King Center Collections List, 2011 (Box 5)
  - ASDAH Notes and Civil Rights Movement in Hale County, undated (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Will Dunn, 1986 July (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Katie and Nat Richardson, undated (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Joe Reidy, 1984 January 14 (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Index of Tapes, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Plantation as Historical Laboratory, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Tunica, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Mississippi Interviews: Tunica Newsweek Article, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Articles, 1982, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Talk at Warren Center, 2009 April 5 (Box 5)
  - Talk at Wilson Library, 2011 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Developmental Editors: Shari Cauldron, 2013 March 21 (Box 5)
  - Developmental Editors: Madeleine Adams, 2015 July 6 (Box 5)
  - Harvard University Press: Proposal, undated (Box 5)
  - Harvard University Press: 2017 Catalog (Box 5)
  - Backstory, 2017 (Box 5)
  - Photo Album, circa 1980s (Box 5)
    Photographs used as illustrations in A Mind to Stay, with a list of captions. 41 color prints.
  - Hall County Background; Tunica, 1978; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0017)
  - Leuchtenberg, January 21; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0044)
  - Drive Into Cassimore, 1978 August 17; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0001)
  - Cassimore Church Service: Carrie Davis, 1978 August 20; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0110)
  - Cassimore Church Service, 1978 August 20; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0112)
  - Cassimore Church Service, 1978 August 21; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0111)
  - Horton Grove Interview: McDaniel, Haskins, 1980 June; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0053)
  - Horton Grove Interview: McDaniel; Stagville Site Survey, 1980 June; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0054)
  - Walter Jackson, 1981 May 2; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0162)
  - Richardson Gospel Anniversary, 1981 May 3; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0102)
  - Richardson Gospel Anniversary, 1981 May 3; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0103)
  - Washboard Slim, 1981 November 5; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0128)
  - SN Talk at Beaufort, NC Wesleyan Faculty, 1982 August 25; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0119)
  - Bernice Reagon; George McDaniel; Columbus, 1982 May; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0055)
  - Afro-American Local History Talk, 1982 May; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0117)
  - Historical Society of N.C., 1983 April 22; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0167)
  - Labor Leadership Seminar Tape 3: Paul Luebre, "Labor Power at City Hall", 1983 April 23; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0101)
  - Questions re: Erasmus Talk, 1983 January 24; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0161)
  - Campus Club Lecture; Thomas Huber Conversation, 1983 January 26-27; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0160)
  - Cassimore Homecoming, 1983 July 3; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0071)
  - Cassimore Homecoming, 1983 July 3; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0072)
  - Cassimore Church Services Tape 1, 1983 June 19; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0062)
  - Cassimore Church Services Tape 2, 1983 June 19; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0063)
  - Darcey, 1984 July; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0122)
  - Horton Grove Slave Quarters; Converastion with Addie Cameron and others, 1986 February 22; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0061)
  - Cassimore Homecoming, 1986 July 6; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0034)
  - Cassimore Service and Homecoming, 1986 July 6; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0035)
  - Endesha Ida Mae Holland: Memories of Mississippi Delta, 1987 January 23; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0040)
  - Endesha Ida Mae Holland: Memories of Mississippi Delta, 1987 January 24; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0039)
  - Sounds of the South and Church Music, 1988 July 1; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0158)
  - Cassimore Homecoming, 1988 July 3; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0036)
  - Cameron Grove, undated; audiocassette (Box 6, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0033)
  - Chapter 13: Chafe, undated; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0056)
  - Say Amen, Somebody (1 of 2), undated; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0057)
  - Say Amen, Somebody (2 of 2), undated; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0058)
  - untitled, undated; audiocassette (Box 7, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0059)
  - Shoshana Bat Mitzah 1, undated; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0096)
  - Shoshana Bat Mitzah 2, undated; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0097)
  - Labor Leadership Seminar Tape 1: Sin and Jackie Hall, undated; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0099)
  - Labor Leadership Seminar Tape 2, undated; audiocassette (Box 8, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0100)
  - Miss Tunica; Long? Richmond?, undated; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0124)
  - untitled, undated; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0125)
  - untitled, undated; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0126)
  - untitled, undated; audiocassette (Box 9, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0127)
  - McDaniel, undated; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0163)
  - KOL and Son?, undated; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0164)
  - Folk Festival, undated; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0165)
  - Folk Festival, undated; audiocassette (Box 10, Audio-cassette UA29020130-CS-0166)